Finding Aid for Arthur J. Lacy Papers, 1891-1975
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Legal Files
  - Law Office miscellaneous
    - Anderson, Wilcox and Lacy, office manual, undated (Box 10)
Cold war Family correspondence [in folders 198-202] and notes [in folders 250-269].
Crime Essay, "Crime and Criminals", Feb. 1913 [in folder 241].
Depression--1929--Michigan See speeches [in folders 221-223]; family papers [in folders 188-194]; and papers [in folders 65-116].
Detroit Bar Association Papers, Feb. 16, 1945 [in folder 126] and Apr. 2, 1946 [in folder 128].
Detroit Trust Company. Paper June 2, 1936, "An analysis of Detroit Trust Company [in box 10]; and correspondence throughout.
Detroit (Mich.). Mayor's Committee on Youth Problems. Letter to George F. Boos, Oct. 5, 1950.
Ford Motor Company. Relating to the Ford Stock Tax Case [in box 10]
Hawaii Annexation of Hawaii, especially in debating notes, 1894-1895 [in folder 230].
Hiss, Alger Letter to Dr. George Kellinger, chairman of the U.S. Parole Board, Nov. 16, 1952.
Juvenile delinquency--Michigan Essay, "Parental Delinquency, April 1914 [in folder 241]
Labor unions--Michigan Letter to Mayor C. Wolff, July 11, 1940
League of Nations Essay, Nov. 16, 1920 [in folder 242]
Michigan. Commission on the Codification of Laws. Letters to Woodbridge N. Ferris, Apr. 16, 1913 and May 21, 1913; letter to Lacy, June 25, 1913; and Report on the Committee on Codification of Laws, July 14, 1913 [in box 46].
Michigan--Emigration and immigration Essay, 1913-1914 [in folder 241] and notes, Jan. 9, 1915.
Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913- Letter to Arthur Summerfield, Sept. 1952 [in folder 143]; letter to Frank Lacy, Feb. 19, 1951 [in folder 200]; and letter to Robert Moylan, Nov. 5, 1960.
Philippines--History--1898-1946 Extract of letter, May 9, 1899 [in folder 167]
Plunkett, Horace Curzon, Sir, 1854-1932. Notes, Jan. 20, 1920 and correspondence files during the 1920's.
Prohibition--Michigan Volstead Act, especially unmarked notes, 1923 [in folder 57]; and correspondence with Louis A. Culliner, Mar. 9, 1927 [in folder 62]
Sit-down strikes--Michigan Letter to Joseph Garwick, March 15, 1937.
Taxation--Michigan Speeches, 1930-1932 [in folders 221-223]; essays, 1930-1931 [in folder 243]; and undated notes [in folder 247]
Trusts, Industrial Speech before the Lewis Cass Club, Dec. 21, 1962 [in folder 217]
United States. Army--History--Punitive Expedition into Mexico, 1916. See letters to Kenneth O. Garwick, Oct. 1, and Nov. 12, 1916 [in folder 184]
United States. Constitution. Speeches [in folder 224] and notes throughout
United States. Labor Management Relations Act, 1947. Letters to Arthur Vandenberg, Homer Ferguson, and George D. O'Brien, Feb. 26, 1949 [in folder 136]
Women's Rights--United States Letter to his parents, Jan. 3, 1897 [in folder 18]; essay, 1912, "The Dignity of Housework" [in folder 241]; and notes, June 12, 1910.
Women--Suffrage--United States Letter to Manda Garwicke, 1913 [in folder 45]; letter to Fred M. Butzel, Oct. 22, 1918; correspondence with A.R. Canfield, Apr. 10 and 18, 1923; and debating notes, 1895 [in folder 230].
World War, 1914-1948 Correspondence [in folders 51-53] and notes, Mar. 4, 1915-Oct. 21, 1920.
World War, 1914-1918--Finance--United States Liberty Loan campaigns during World War I, especially memorandum of addresses during second Liberty Loan Campaign, Oct. 1917.
World War, 1939-1945 Correspondence [in folders 116-125]; family papers [in folders 195-197]; and notes [in folders 248-249].